const acronymCardData = [
    {
        "Front":"U.S.C",
        "Back" :"United States Code"
    },
    {
        "Front":"SP",
        "Back" :"Special Publication"
    },
    {
        "Front":"SCAP",
        "Back" :"Security Content Automation Protocol"
    },
    {
        "Front":"RMF",
        "Back" :"Risk Management Framework"
    },
    {
        "Front":"POAM",
        "Back" :"Plan of Actions and Milestones"
    },
    {
        "Front":"PKI",
        "Back" :"Public Key Infrastructure"
    },
    {
        "Front":"OMB",
        "Back" :"Office of Mangement and Budget"
    },
    {
        "Front":"ODNI",
        "Back" :"Office of the Direcotr of National Intelligence"
    },
    {
        "Front":"OCIL",
        "Back" :"Open Checklist Interactive Language"
    },
    {
        "Front":"NSA",
        "Back" :"National Security Agency"
    },
    {
        "Front":"NIST",
        "Back" :"National Institute of Standards and Technology"
    },
    {
        "Front":"NCP",
        "Back" :"National Checklist Program"
    },
    {
        "Front":"ISO",
        "Back" :"International Organization for Standardization"
    },
    {
        "Front":"IEC",
        "Back" :"International Electrotechnical Commission"
    },
    {
        "Front":"ICS",
        "Back" :"Industrial Control System"
    },
    {
        "Front":"FISMA",
        "Back" :"Federal Information Security Mangement Act"
    },
    {
        "Front":"FIPS",
        "Back" :"Federal Information Processing Standards"
    },
    {
        "Front":"DoD",
        "Back" :"Department of Defense"
    },
    {
        "Front":"COTS",
        "Back" :"Commercial Off-the-Shelf"
    },
    {
        "Front":"CUI",
        "Back" :"Controlled Unclassified Information"
    },
    {
        "Front":"CNSS",
        "Back" :"Committee on National Security Systems"
    },


]

export default acronymCardData;